Now we're going to do a little coloring on our clown face to really clown it up.
Give it some clown makeup.
So I'm going to do those big eyes with the nice permanent marker.
You want to do just a big arch over both of the eyes like that with nice bright colors.
Then I'm going to make the eye look bigger by using a black and just fill that it.
That will make the eye look a little bit bigger, really wide eyed clown.
You have to be careful not to touch the marker.
Let it dry completely or you can smudge.
I made a little smudge here.
If you do that, you can always cover it up with some decoration later.
Now I'm going to make some nice big eyebrows with this red.
Even though it is a permanent marker, you want to wait just a little bit on the fun foam to let it dry so that because it will smudge if you touch it right away after.
Now we'll finish up our clown by adding a little bit of hair on the sides.
You want to put a good amount of glue here on both sides.
And then we'll add our fuzzy hair and then we'll finish off with we're going to dot some glue, just some little dots of glue here and there.
And use these red and blue sequins just here and there to brighten up our clown.
And there's our finished clown mask.